Next is Kyoto, where I will be going on a national concert hall tour on Sunday, June 4.
The event will be held at the Uji City Cultural Center Main Hall, and I'm very excited because this will be the first time I've been to Kyoto.
It will be the first time for me to go to Kyoto for a super time war, so I am very excited about it.
I already have a lot of souvenirs and things I want to buy.
But I've heard a lot of things from you guys this time.
I'm looking forward to going because I've heard a lot of things from you guys and there are more things that I want to try.
Now, I would like to introduce them to you all.
I'd like to introduce you all to some ochazuke!
First, Arashiyama's Kijuro Steak Soup.
It's also possible to eat it with dashi broth.
It's definitely delicious, isn't it?
The next stop was a café called Kumo no Cha where they had cloud shaped sweets.
And the beverages were stylish and looked delicious!
I was informed that Inari-san has black sesame seeds in it.
Uji City in Kyoto, where the Inari Festival is held, is famous for its matcha green tea!
Matcha! Matcha!
That's why we are recommending the following stores!
Ito Kyuemon and Nakamura Toukichi.
I've been to Nakamura Tokichi before.
I'm in Tokyo and I love matcha.
I went with a friend once and it was delicious!
Also, Matsuba's Nishin-soba is good.
Nishin is a fish, right?
Nishin-soba.
And the sugarinosoba "motsu tsukemen" (noodles with pork and vegetables).
Next is Sweets Cafe Kyoto Keizo!
Oh! Wow, it looks like you can eat Mont Blanc with a 10 minute shelf life!
10 minute shelf life means you have to eat it right after it's made!
You can only eat Mont Blanc here!
Next is a store called Ishidatami on Nichinenzaka. They use high quality matcha green tea.
I want to try it!
I love green tea ice cream!
There are many ramen shops in Kawaramachi, so if you like ramen, you should go there!
Also, there's a bread only available in Kyoto called "Carne" from Shizutani.
It's like a sandwich with margarine, onions and ham inside!
I looked it up, and many people say it's delicious. I'd like to try it!
And Guignol. Shimogahara.
There's shaved ice with fresh squeezed strawberries on page 1.
It looked delicious!
And Kyoto Ramen!
Shinpuku Saikan's main store.
Another ramen shop!
I'm not sure where to go if you like ramen!
Next is the seasonal fruit sandwiches at Ichikawa-ya Coffee in Higashiyama!
Oh, this also looks delicious! Fruit sandwiches!
I looked at it, and the fruit pulp looks good too I looked at it, and it has big pieces of fruit pulp in it, and it looks good
Also...
Ichimonjiya, located at Imamiya Shrine, is said to have delicious roasted rice cakes!
I want to try it!
It is said to be a traditional taste from the Heian period (794-1192).
Next is Saga's croquette in Arashiyama!
I love croquettes! Next, a Japanese cafe in the market!
There's also a Japanese cafe in the market, Kinone, with strawberry parfait and shaved ice!
Matcha ice cream with matcha powder.
Uji Matcha Parfait.
And Tokura's juicy hamburger steak.
And then there's Matcha House.
It's called Matcha House.
Matcha House Matchakan!
Matcha Tiramisu in a bath!
I hear it's highly recommended.
I love it! It's so good!
I've had the tiramisu in a bus before.
I had a tiramisu in a bus once, and it was delicious!
But this place...
Matcha House Matchakan has many other matcha sweets.
Also, there's a place called Onomatopoeia Komori.
They have a matcha buffet in a Japanese-style room, and you can enjoy Japanese sweets in a Japanese-style room.
Houhi and Housen are popular local restaurants.
Houhi and Hosen are popular local restaurants.
Next is a souvenir, Mangetsudo's Karinto Manju green tea buns!
I love it!
I love karinto manju!
I'm curious!
Otsu no Sato
Since the end of the Edo period
has been dedicated to making pickled plums
Famous in Kyoto
There is a store specializing in pickled plums
And
There is a famous store in Kyoto specializing in pickled plums
And I checked out the voice doughnut
and colorful, and I thought they would be very happy if I bought them as souvenirs.
I think they will be very happy if you buy them as souvenirs!
And there were so many of them!
I feel like I won't be able to eat the other ones after eating this one.
I've never had it!
I wonder if they sell it before I go home.
Also, I heard that the white rice cakes from the original shop in Nishio are really good!
It's made of white rice cake and topped with soybean flour and molasses.
I want to try this too!
And I often buy these as souvenirs for the Tokisen members too!
Okoi Cha Hondan Chocolat from Mar Blanche!
It's called "Chanohana" (tea flower).
It's really delicious!
It's really delicious, isn't it?
I know what you mean.
I love it!
They also have a tea langue d'ocher.
They also have a delicious langue d'ocher with roasted tea.Okoicha langdosha is also delicious. I often buy it!
Also, I found out that they have Okoicha julienne, and I'm a little curious about that too!
I'll definitely buy some!
I wonder if they sell it. I want to buy it!
I hope so!
Also, Futaba's Mame-Daifuku, Midori-juan...
It's a cute and fashionable kompaitou from Shimizu. It's cute, and they have different flavors and types!
And Buckwheat Bowls, they are in the shape of a flower and are addictive!
I heard that the sweets of a store called "Nisshiki Marun" are cute, like the shape of the side, and they are really cute!
Also, Kyoto Fruit Daifuku Kajuan. I love fruit daifuku!
I want some! Also, Shichamiya Sansho is really good!
I heard that the shichimi from Shichamiya Honpo is delicious!
It's so good that it will change the concept of shichimi I've had so far!
I can't wait to try it!
I also heard that Kyo Balm and the birthday chocolates from Cacao 365 in Kioto, Kyoto
It's also interesting and fashionable.
Next, I'd like to introduce some sightseeing spots.
The Heidoin Temple in Uji City, which is also the design of the 10-yen coin.
Hodo
Please visit there!
Next, I'd like to introduce you to a sightseeing spot.
33 Gendo
This is a place called
I heard it's close to the station.
What a surprise!
There are more than 1,000 Kannon statues here.
There are more than 1,000 Kannon statues here, so I think it's a valuable place.
The Kannon is a deity of the Japanese Goddess of Mercy, and there are more than 1,000 Kannon statues here, so this is a valuable place.
It's nice to eat while enjoying the cool breeze.
I'm sure it tastes even better if you eat while enjoying the cool breeze.
Kimono Forest I once took a trip to Kyoto a long time ago.
I once went on a trip to Kyoto.
We rented yukata.
And Kyoto Metropolitan Sauna.
Hakusan Hot Spring
Water bath
Even if you are not good at it, you can go in at all.
I'm curious about the quality of the sauna.
I have been in a sauna for a while, but
but I haven't enjoyed the feeling of being in shape yet.
I'd like to try it someday.
Next, let's go to the bamboo grove in Arashiyama.
Bamboo grove in Arashiyama
I also went to Kiyomizu-dera Temple.
And Kiyomizu-dera Temple
I went to Kiyomizu-dera Temple on a restoration trip a long time ago.
Kyoto Aquarium
It's just a short walk from Kyoto Station.
It's just a short walk from Kyoto station.
They have penguins and dolphins.
Nice!
They have a dolphin show too!
I'm curious about a lot of penguins too... I'm curious about a lot of penguins too...
Next
Fushiminari-taisha
Senbon Torii (Thousand torii gates)
And this one too!
I wanted to go there!
I wanted to go.
It's nice.
It was so beautiful.
There were so many torii gates.
And then...
Kurumazaki Shrine
Kurumazaki-jinja Shrine, a shrine for the performing arts.
I went this far...
I started to run away from the shrine.
And there seems to be a Shimoga Shrine.
I have an image of a shrine
Everyone
Please go there.
Enjoy Kyoto while having fun!
I hope this has been of some help to you!
Thank you very much for sharing your experiences with us!
I look forward to seeing you in Kyoto!
Thank you for watching until the end of the week!
Bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye!
crackle, crackle, crackle, crackle, crackle, crackle!
crackle, crackle, crackle, crackle, crackle, crackle, crackle, crackle!
crackle, crackle, crackle, crackle
crackling, crackling, crackling, crackling, crackling
Pops!
Crackling!
Subscribe to our channel!